adbucks.com 2017-02-21

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. This Privacy Policy governs your use of the AdBucks.com website and service (the "Site", "we" or "us"). As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future and it is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy from time to time and the effective date listed with it.

## Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety

Your name, physical address, phone number and password are considered confidential. However, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system.

## Information Collected From You

During sign up we require that you provide certain information that may include Account Data (i.e., your name, physical address, email address, phone number, username, email addresses, and password) and Use Information (IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding search history, browsing history, registration, deposit information, advertisements submitted in connection with advertising bids and purchases and user history).

## How is this Information Used?

We do not collect or store any financial data. All payments to the Site are done through transfers from your PayPal, wire transfer and other similar mechanisms. Information will be stored regarding all purchases and transfers to the Site for the purpose of administering your account and processing advertising purchases made through your account.

We may use "cookies" and Use Information to better your experience on the Site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Site according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Use Information. Aggregate, non-individual membership Use Information may be shared with third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products or services we believe you may be interested in.

We may also share the aggregate Demographic Information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the Site.

## Changing Your Information

You will have the ability to review, add to and change your information through the Site. The Site reserves the right to alter or eliminate this ability at any time. The Site may retain records regarding when information was added, altered or deleted.

## Emails From Us and use of Your Email Address

Your email address will be used by us to contact you when we have special offers or other information to provide you. Such information may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to your account and other information related to your membership to the Site. We may send you emails prior to and after you have terminated your membership to our service until such time as you advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you no longer wish to receive email from us. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us please unsubscribe by using this link: [Link], or send us an email to [Email]. We and our advertising partners fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act and as such all emails from us and our advertising partners will always, among other required disclosures, have a place for you to opt out of receipt of further email correspondence. Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our marketing partners without your consent. **Please immediately report any emails you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purport to promote the Site.**

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes. Instead it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. No change in the privacy policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless the privacy policy has clear language indicating otherwise.

## Changes in the Ownership of the Site

The Site is a growing online service. As such, we may have the occasion to buy or sell assets, including, but not limited to, in connection with a merger, dissolution, and transfer of ownership. Depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us (including Account Data and Use Information) with third parties, as necessary to initiate, investigate or complete any such transaction(s).

Last updated: Wednesday, 02-Jul-14 17:14:05 PDT
